https://www.danceumbrella.co.uk/privacy/

Skip to content
Home ›
Privacy Policy
Privacy StatementDance Umbrella is committed to protecting our customers, donors, artists and partners privacy and takes its responsibility regarding the security of their personal information very seriously. We will be clear and transparent about the information we are collecting and what we will do with that information.
danceumbrella.co.uk, the Dance Umbrella Website, has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site. Please visit Dance Umbrella Privacy Policy for our full policy terms.
CookiesSome of the pages on our site contain embedded content from third-party websites – like a video from YouTube for example which may use Cookies. These are known as 3rd party Cookies. Please see below for information about the specific 3rd party Cookies used on our site.
Because this content is from another website, we don’t control the setting of these cookies. If you want to change your cookie preferences, check the third-party websites for information on how to manage their cookies.
For more information on how to manage, delete and control Cookies on your computer please visit http://www.aboutcookies.org/
Google AnalyticsThese cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form that does not identify a visitor, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited. This helps us to improve the way our website works, for example by making sure users are finding what they need easily.
Click here for an overview of privacy at Google
To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit the Google site.
YouTube cookiesWe embed videos from YouTube. This mode may set cookies on your computer once you click on the YouTube video player, but YouTube will not store personally-identifiable cookie information for playbacks of embedded videos using the privacy-enhanced mode.
To find out more watch YouTube’s video about Privacy with videos
Facebook and Twitter cookiesWe embed feeds from Facebook and Twitter. The site does not use cookies to create a profile of your browsing behaviour on third-party sites or to show you ads, although it may use anonymous or aggregate data to improve ads generally. You can remove or block cookies using the settings in your browser, but in some cases, this may impact your ability to use Facebook and Twitter.
To find out more visit Facebook’s Cookie policy
For Twitter’s Cookie policy
Add This cookiesThere are a number of social cookies that let you share/like/tweet etc. all of our pages using your preferred social networks and websites. If you are logged into any of these sites, the addthis cookies keep you logged in, and help you share the content.
The AddThis privacy policy is here
HotJarHotJar is a service we use to understand how users interact with our website. It generates online surveys, creates heatmaps and videos showing use of the website.
To function properly, Hotjar stores first-party cookies on your visitor’s browser. Cookies are set by the Hotjar script.
Hotjar cookies are responsible for displaying the correct content to our visitors without personally identifying anyone.
WooCommerce CookiesWe use WooCommerce to manage e-commerce transactions through our website such as donations, memberships and other sales. No personal information is stored within these cookies. For more information about how WooCommerce use cookies visit their website
Stripe - Payment GatewayWe use Stripe as a global payment processor through WooCommerce on this website.Stripe does not sell or rent Personal Data to marketers or unaffiliated third parties. You can read their global privacy policy.  They cookies to ensure
that their Services function properly,
detect and prevent fraud,
analyze and improve Services.
You can read more about their cookie policy on their website
MailchimpWe use Mailchimp to manage our emailing list. Forms are embedded into our website but you may visit the Mailchimp hosted features to manage your data on our account. You can learn more about the use of cookies by Mailchimp on their website
Public ForumsThis site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
Contact details and further information Please get in contact with us if you have any questions about this privacy policy, and in particular if you would like to object to any processing of your personal information that we carry out for our legitimate organisational interests.
Please also contact us if you have any questions about the information we hold about you, or to change your contact preferences with us:
Email: admin@danceumbrella.co.uk
Post: Data Protection Officer at Dance Umbrella, Somerset House, West Wing, Strand, London WC2R 1LA
Support usDance Umbrella Digital is free to attend but not free to make.
In these uncertain times we would love your support in any of the following ways:Make a donationSign up to our mailing list Share content with friendsGive us feedback
